annieselke.com 2019-01-23

# Annie Selke Privacy Policy | Annie Selke

Updated Privacy Policy February 2017

## OUR COMMITMENT TO PRIVACY

This policy describes the personal information we collect about you, why we collect it, how we use it, and when we share it with third parties. Our policy also describes the choices you can make about how we collect and use your information. If our information practices change, we will post an updated policy on our website. You can tell if the policy has changed by checking the revision date that appears above. If we change the policy in a material way, we will provide appropriate notice to you. You may exercise your choices about how we collect and use your information consistent with this policy at any time. We at The Annie Selke Companies are committed to ensuring our customers' privacy on the Internet. We preserve and use your customer information in a manner that is intended to maintain the relationship and trust that we have with you.

By visiting www.annieselke.com™ and using affiliated websites, you accept the practices as described in the following Privacy Notice.

#### PERSONAL INFORMATION

We collect personal information, such as your name, email address, postal address, phone number, or credit card number when you visit our website, place an order online or by phone, use our App, save your information with us on line, contact us with a question or concern, or participate in a contest, promotion or survey. We also collect anonymous information to help improve the content and relevancy of our website, enhance our customer service, personalize the content and layout for visitors, and generally enhance our customers' buying experience. We may wish to communicate with you from time to time via e-mail to provide you with information regarding your account. On occasion, the information gathered through the website might be used to customize your information or update you on new products or promotions. You may also contact us to update your address or let us know of changes. 

#### OTHER WAYS WE MAY USE INFORMATION WE COLLECT

We may use information to:   
Fulfill your requests for products and services;   
Offer products and services we believe may be of interest to you;  
Customize the advertising and content that you see on our Services;   
Facilitate use of our Services;   
Manage your account and your preferences;   
Analyze use of and improve our Services, products, and other services;  
Identify and protect against fraudulent transactions and other misuses of our Services;   
Enforce our conditions of use. 

In the unlikely event of a sale or merger of The Annie Selke Companies or substantially all of its assets are acquired, customer information may be one of the transferred business assets. 

Additionally, we may release account information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law; enforce or apply our Terms of Use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of www.annieselke.com™ or our users, or others. This might include exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. 

#### HOW DOES THE ANNIE SELKE COMPANIES USE COOKIES AND OTHER TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES?

As with many websites, we use "cookies" to obtain certain types of information when you access www.annieselke.com™ and affiliated websites. Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that are transferred to your computer's hard drive to enable our systems to recognize your browser. Accepting cookies allows you to take advantage of all features available on our websites. (The "Help" portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to prevent receiving cookies altogether.) We use "pixel tags" (also called "web beacons" or "clear gifs"), which are tiny graphic images, on our Website, App and in our emails. Pixel tags help us analyze our customers' online behavior and measure the effectiveness of our marketing programs. We work with service providers that help us track, collect, and analyze this information. 

Pixel tags may be used to collect information about your visit, including the pages you view, the features you use, the links you click, and other actions you take in connection with the Website. This information may include your computer's Internet protocol (IP) address, your browser type, your operating system, date and time information, and other technical information about your computer. We may also track certain information about the identity of the website you visited immediately before coming to our site. 

Pixel tags and cookies in our emails may be used to track your interactions with those messages, such as when you receive, open, or click a link in an email message from us. Information such as your gender, birthday, zip code, as well as other information, such as your preferred means of communication, is collected when you voluntarily provide this information. Unless combined with personal information, this information does not personally identify you or any other user of the Website. Aggregated personal information does not personally identify you or any other user of the Website. 

#### HOW DO I KNOW MY PERSONAL INFORMATION IS SECURE?

We do our best to provide you with a safe and convenient shopping experience. We have in place certain physical, electronic, contractual, and managerial safeguards to protect the security and privacy of your personal information.

When you enter your personal information on our websites, we use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology to protect your information as it is transmitted to us. To make sure you are accessing our secure server before you submit personal financial information, look at the lower left-hand corner of your browser. If you see an unbroken key or a closed lock (depending upon your browser), then SSL is active. To double-check for security, look at the URL or Location line of your browser. If you have accessed a secure server, the first characters of the address in that line should change from "http" to "https."

If for any reason you cannot access the secure server, or if you're not quite comfortable shopping online at any of our websites, please feel free to place your order with us by telephone at the number listed in the section entitled, "How do I contact you?", below.

#### HOW IS MY INFORMATION USED FOR BEHAVIORAL OR INTERNET-BASED ADVERTISING?

We work with third-party companies that use tracking technologies (including cookies and pixel tags) on our websites in order to provide tailored advertisements on our behalf and on behalf of other advertisers across the Internet. These companies may collect information about your activity on our sites and your interaction with our advertising and other communications and use this information to determine which ads you see on third-party websites and applications. For more information about this practice and to understand your options, please visit [http://www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/).  Third-party vendors, including Google, show ads for our websites on the Internet, and use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to our websites. Users may opt out of Google’s use of cookies by visiting the Google advertising opt-out page at <http://www.google.com/ads/preferences>, and opt out of a third-party vendor’s use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising initiative opt-out page at <http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/>.

#### WHAT ABOUT LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES?

For your convenience and information, our websites may contain links to other sites which may have privacy policies that differ from our own. We are not responsible for the content or practices of any linked site. We encourage you to read the posted privacy statement and user terms and conditions whenever interacting with, and prior to, providing any personal information to any other website.

#### CATALOG MAILING LIST

If you no longer wish to receive catalogs from Annie Selke, please [click here](mailto:info@annieselke.com) or contact us at 877-586-4771. In order to remove you from our list, you must provide your name and mailing address as shown on your catalog. We will remove your name from our mailing list as soon as possible. Please keep in mind that you may receive another catalog before we are able to remove you from our mailing list. On occasion, we may share information from our catalog mailing list with our business partners. If you do not want your name and address shared with other organizations, contact us at 877-586-4771. 

#### HOW DO I CONTACT YOU?

For questions about our policy, to make choices about receiving promotional communications, updates to your personal information, or to place an order, you can contact any of our brands by email, telephone, or postal mail:

Customer Service

125 Pecks Rd

Pittsfield, MA  01201

877 586 4771

The Outlet at Pine Cone Hill

800 442 8157
